https://www.lhf.org/privacy-policy/

CURRENT HOURS: Closed for touring, Open by reservation for Programs and Events LHF Blog | LHF KidsMEMBERSHIPVOLUNTEERDONATE
Visit
Hours and Admission2020 Season Guest FAQAbout the FarmsAccessibilityFirst Time VisitorsPhoto PolicyVisitor GuidesPurchase TicketsEvents & Programs
Upcoming EventsDay CampsHistoric Dinners & TeasBarnyard Readers Preschool ProgramsHistoric Skills ClassesHistoric BaseballBehind the Scenes ToursFarmstasia GalaSchools & Groups
K-12 SchoolsHomeschool GroupsGroup Reservations for Youth (Scouts, 4-H, daycares)Group Reservations for AdultsHistoric Home ToursHistory Speaker ProgramFrequently Asked QuestionsMembership
Purchase or RenewMembershipMember BenefitsFrequently Asked QuestionsAbout Us
About UsPresident’s MessageAnnual ReportBoard of DirectorsManagement TeamRental FacilitiesSaint Pope John Paul II VisitOnline Collections DatabaseShopContact Us
Search Button:
Toggle navigation
MENU Visit
Hours and Admission2020 Season Guest FAQAbout the FarmsAccessibilityFirst Time VisitorsPhoto PolicyVisitor GuidesPurchase TicketsEvents & Programs
Upcoming EventsDay CampsHistoric Dinners & TeasBarnyard Readers Preschool ProgramsHistoric Skills ClassesHistoric BaseballBehind the Scenes ToursFarmstasia GalaSchools & Groups
K-12 SchoolsHomeschool GroupsGroup Reservations for Youth (Scouts, 4-H, daycares)Group Reservations for AdultsHistoric Home ToursHistory Speaker ProgramFrequently Asked QuestionsMembership
Purchase or RenewMembershipMember BenefitsFrequently Asked QuestionsAbout Us
About UsPresident’s MessageAnnual ReportBoard of DirectorsManagement TeamRental FacilitiesSaint Pope John Paul II VisitOnline Collections DatabaseShopContact Us  volunteer donate
Search Button:
Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyWe respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.Security PolicyYour payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.Return PolicyAll refunds will be provided as a credit to the credit card used at the time of purchase within five (5) business days upon receipt of the returned merchandise or approved refund request.  If the credit card used at the time of purchase is no longer valid, the refund will be processed via check and mailed to the original purchaser via U.S. Postal Service (USPS) within ten (10) business days.Shipping PolicyItems purchased from our online store that require shipping will be shipped out within five (5) business days of purchase. We determine the most efficient shipping carrier for your order. The carriers used are: U.S. Postal Service (USPS), United Parcel Service (UPS) or FedEx. Sorry but we cannot ship to P.O. Boxes. If you’re trying to estimate when a package will be delivered, please note the following: Credit card authorization and verification must be received prior to processing. Federal Express and UPS deliveries occur Monday through Friday, excluding holidays. For specific shipping questions or requests, contact retail@lhf.org.Sign Up For OurNEWSLETTER Your NameEmail CAPTCHA
Facebook Icon:
Twitter Icon:
Instagram Icon:
Youtube Icon:
AccoladesVisitor Code of ConductEmploymentInternshipsSitemapPrivacy Policy
Living History Farms, 11121 Hickman Road, Urbandale, IA 50322, (515)278-5286THANK YOU TO OUR 2020 PREMIER PARTNERS: Bravo Greater Des Moines, C. Robert & Babette C. Brenton, John Deere, and WHO-HD Channel 13. Copyright © 2020 Living History Farms. All Rights Reserved. Des Moines Web Design by Webspec Design
Print this page
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
Yotube
